University Council; Records ua100
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Meeting Records, 1844-2015; 2; 6.33 cubic ft. 139 Digital Files
  - Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 2 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 4)
  - Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 2 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 5)
  - Refreshment, 1980-1983 (Box 2 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 6)
  - Meeting, 1981 January 26 (Box 2 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 7)
  - Minutes and Agenda, 1981 January-1985 June (Box 2 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 8)
  - Meeting, 1981 February 23 (Box 2 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 9)
  - Meeting, 1981 March 26 (Box 2 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 10)
  - Meeting, 1981 April 27 (Box 2 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 11)
  - Meeting, 1981 May 28 (Box 2 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 12)
  - Annual Meeting, 1981 May 28 (Box 2 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 13)
  - Meeting, 1981 July 14 (Box 2 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 14)
  - Meeting, 1981 September 24 (Box 2 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 15)
  - Meeting, 1981 December 3 (Box 2 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 16)
  - Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 2 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 17)
  - Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 2 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 18)
  - Meeting, 1982 January 18 (Box 2 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 19)
  - Meeting, 1982 January 25 (Box 2 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 20)
  - Retreats, 1982 February 26 (Box 2 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 21)
  - Meeting, 1982 March 24 (Box 2 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 22)
  - Meeting, 1982 May 4 (Box 2 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 23)
  - Meeting, 1982 May 4 (Box 2 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 24)
  - Meeting, 1982 September 9 (Box 2 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 25)
  - Meeting, 1982 October 26 (Box 2 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 26)
  - Meeting, 1982 December 7 (Box 2 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 27)
  - Task Forces, 1982 (Box 2 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 28)
  - Citizen Advisory Committee, 1983 (Box 2 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 29)
  - Committees, 1982-1983 (Box 2 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 30)
  - Meeting, 1983 February 14 (Box 2 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 31)
  - Meeting, 1983 March 1 (Box 2 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 32)
  - Meeting, 1983 April 26 (Box 2 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 33)
  - Meeting, 1983 June 14 (Box 2 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 34)
  - Meeting, 1983 October 25 (Box 2 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 35)
  - Meeting, 1983 December 8 (Box 2 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 36)
  - Regional Advisory Committee, 1983 (Box 2 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 37)
  - Special Brunch, 1983 September 19 (Box 2 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 38)
  - Meeting, 1983 September 13 (Box 2 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 39)
  - Meeting, 1984 September 13 (Box 2 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 40)
  - Committees, 1984 (Box 2 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 41)
  - Meeting, 1984 January 26 (Box 2 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 42)
  - Meeting, 1984 March 1 (Box 2 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 43)
  - Meeting, 1984 April 5 (Box 2 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 44)
  - Meeting, 1984 May 17 (Box 2 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 45)
  - Meeting, 1984 June 28 (Box 2 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 46)
  - Meeting, 1984 September 13 (Box 2 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 47)
  - Meeting, 1984 November 1 (Box 2 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 48)
  - Meeting, 1984 December 20 (Box 2 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 49)
  - Meeting, 1985 February 28 (Box 2 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 50)
  - Meeting, 1985 April 4 (Box 3 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 1)
  - Meeting, 1985 May 9 (Box 3 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 2)
  - Meeting, 1985 June 27 (Box 3 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 3)
  - Agendas and minutes of meetings, 1985 July 1-1985 June 30 (Box 3 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 4)
  - Committees, 1985 (Box 3 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 5)
  - Meeting, 1985 September 26 (Box 3 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 6)
  - Meeting, 1986 January 30 (Box 3 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 7)
  - Meeting, 1986 March 27 (Box 3 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 8)
  - Meeting, 1986 May 8 (Box 3 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 9)
  - Meeting, 1986 June 24 (Box 3 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 10)
  - Agendas and minutes of meetings, 1986 July 1-1987 June 30 (Box 3 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 11)
  - Meeting, 1986 September 23 (Box 3 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 12)
  - Meeting, 1986 December 9 (Box 3 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 13)
  - Committee, 1986 (Box 3 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 14)
  - Meeting, 1987 February 3 (Box 3 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 15)
  - Meeting, 1987 March 24 (Box 3 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 16)
  - Meeting, 1987 May 12 (Box 3 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 17)
  - Meeting, 1987 June 23 (Box 3 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 18)
  - Agenda and Minutes, 1987 July 1-1988 June 30 (Box 3 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 19)
  - Annual report of the council to the chair of the board of the trustees, 1987 July 1-1988 June 30 (Box 3 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 20)
  - Meeting, 1987 October 28 (Box 3 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 21)
  - Meeting, 1987 November 19 (Box 3 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 22)
  - Annual Reports, 1987-1990 (Box 3 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 23)
  - Agendas and minutes, 1988 July 1-1989 June 30 (Box 3 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 24)
  - Annual report of the council to the chair of the board of the trustees, 1988 July 1-1989 June 19 (Box 3 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 3 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 26)
  - Annual Report, 1989 July 1-1990 June 30 (Box 3 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 27)
  - Special Meeting to view field house plan, 1989 August 10 (Box 3 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 28)
  - Meeting, 1989 September 11 (Box 3 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 29)
  - Meeting, 1989 September 28-1989 September 29 (Box 3 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 30)
  - Meeting, 1989 November 9 (Box 3 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 31)
  - Meeting, 1989 December 21 (Box 3 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 32)
  - University Council Retreat, 1989 (Box 3 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 33)
  - Annual Report, 1989-1990 (Box 3 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 34)
  - General, 1989-1990 (Box 3 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 35)
  - Meeting, 1990 February 8 (Box 3 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 36)
  - Meeting, 1990 May 10 (Box 3 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 37)
  - Meeting, 1990 June 21 (Box 3 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 38)
  - Meeting, 1990 October 4 (Box 3 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 39)
  - Meeting, 1990 November 15 (Box 3 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 40)
  - Meeting, 1990 December 20 (Box 3 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 41)
  - Annual Report, 1990 (Box 3 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 42)
  - Annual Report, 1990-1991 (Box 3 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 43)
  - Evan R. Collins Circle, 1990-1992 (Box 3 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 44)
  - General, 1990-1991 (Box 3 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 45)
  - Meeting, 1991 February 4 (Box 3 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 46)
  - Meeting, 1991 March 28 (Box 3 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 47)
  - Meeting, 1991 May 9 (Box 3 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 48)
  - Meeting, 1991 October 3 (Box 3 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 49)
  - Meeting, 1991 November 7 (Box 3 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 50)
  - University Council Retreat, 1991 November 7-8 (Box 3 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 51)
  - Meeting, 1991 December 19 (Box 4 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1991 (Box 4 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 2)
  - Naming of Evan R. Collins Circle, 1991 (Box 4 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 3)
  - Annual Report, 1991-1992 (Box 4 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 4)
  - Annual Report, 1991-1992 (Box 4 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 5)
  - General, 1991-1992 (Box 4 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 6)
  - General, 1991-1992 (Box 4 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 7)
  - Meeting, 1992 February 13 (Box 4 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 8)
  - Meeting, 1992 March 26 (Box 4 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 9)
  - Meeting, 1992 May 7 (Box 4 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 10)
  - Meeting, 1992 September 24 (Box 4 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 11)
  - Meeting, 1992 November 12 (Box 4 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 12)
  - Meeting, 1992 December 17 (Box 4 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 13)
  - Dean For school of education resumes, 1992 (Box 4 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 14)
  - Annual Report, 1992-1993 (Box 4 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 15)
  - Annual Report, 1992-1993 (Box 4 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 16)
  - General, 1992-1993 (Box 4 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 17)
  - Meeting, 1993 February 11 (Box 4 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 18)
  - Meeting, 1993 March 25 (Box 4 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 19)
  - Meeting, 1993 May 6 (Box 4 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 20)
  - Meeting, 1993 September 23 (Box 4 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 21)
  - Retreat, 1993 November 19-20 (Box 4 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 22)
  - Meeting (gideon putnam hotel), 1993 November 19-20 (Box 4 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 23)
  - Meeting, 1993 December 16 (Box 4 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 24)
  - Annual Report, 1993-1994 (Box 4 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 25)
  - Annual report with agendas and minutes, 1993 July 1-1994 June 30 (Box 4 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 26)
  - General, 1993-1994 (Box 4 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 27)
  - Meeting, 1994 February 10 (Box 4 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 28)
  - Meeting, 1994 March 24 (Box 4 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 29)
  - Meeting, 1994 May 5 (Box 5 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 1)
  - Meeting, 1994 August 8 (Box 5 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 2)
  - Meeting, 1994 September 24 (Box 5 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 3)
  - Meeting, 1994 November 10 (Box 5 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 4)
  - Meeting, 1994 November 10 (Box 5 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 5)
  - Meeting, 1994 December 22 (Box 5 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 6)
  - Annual Report, 1994-1995 (Box 5 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 7)
  - Annual report with agendas and minutes, 1994 July 1-1995 June 30 (Box 5 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 8)
  - General, 1994-1995 (Box 5 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 9)
  - Teleconference, 1995 February 13 (Box 5 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 10)
  - Meeting, 1995 March 2 (Box 5 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 11)
  - Meeting, 1995 March 2 (Box 5 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 12)
  - Meeting, 1995 April 6 (Box 5 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 13)
  - Meeting, 1995 May 18 (Box 5 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 14)
  - Meeting, 1995 September 28 (Box 5 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 15)
  - Meeting, 1995 October 26 (Box 5 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 16)
  - Meeting, 1995 December 7 (Box 5 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 17)
  - Retreat, 1995 December 7-8 (Box 5 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 18)
  - Annual Report, 1995-1996 (Box 5 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 19)
  - Annual Report, 1996 July 1-1997 June 30 (Box 5 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 20)
  - Meeting, 1996 February 8 (Box 5 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 21)
  - Meeting, 1996 March 21 (Box 5 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 22)
  - Meeting, 1996 May 2 (Box 5 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 23)
  - Meeting-Special, 1996 June 13 (Box 5 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 24)
  - Meeting, 1996 September 26 (Box 6 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 1)
  - Meeting, 1996 November 14 (Box 6 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 2)
  - Meeting, 1996 December 19 (Box 6 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 3)
  - Council attendance, 1996 (Box 6 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 4)
  - Annual Report, 1996-1997 (Box 6 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 5)
  - Meeting, 1997 February 13 (Box 6 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 6)
  - Meeting, 1997 March 27 (Box 6 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 7)
  - Meeting, 1997 May 15 (Box 6 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 8)
  - Agendas and Minutes, 1997 July 1-1998 June 30 (Box 6 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 9)
  - Annual Report, 1997-1998 (Box 6 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 10)
  - Agendas and Minutes, 1998 June 30-1998 July 1 (Box 6 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 11)
  - Meeting, 1998 October 1 (Box 6 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 12)
  - Council Retreat, 1998 October 1-2 (Box 6 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 13)
  - Meeting, 1998 November 5 (Box 6 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 14)
  - Meeting, 1998 December 10 (Box 6 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 15)
  - Annual Report, 1998-1999 (Box 6 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 16)
  - Meeting, 1999 January 28 (Box 6 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 17)
  - Meeting, 1999 March 11 (Box 6 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 18)
  - Meeting, 1999 April 29 (Box 6 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 19)
  - Annual Report and minutes of the University Council, 1999 July 1-2000 June 30 (Box 6 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 20)
  - Meeting, 1999 September 16 (Box 6 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 21)
  - Meeting, 1999 November 4 (Box 6 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 22)
  - Meeting, 1999 December 2 (Box 6 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 23)
  - Annual Report, 1999-2000 (Box 6 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 24)
  - Meeting, 2000 January 20 (Box 6 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 25)
  - Meeting, 2000 April 27 (Box 6 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 26)
  - Meeting, 2000 March 2 (Box 6 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 27)
  - Meeting, 2000 September 28 (Box 6 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 28)
  - Meeting, 2000 November 2 (Box 6 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 29)
  - Meeting, 2000 December 7 (Box 6 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 30)
  - Retreat, 2000 December 7-8 (Box 6 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 31)
  - Annual Report, 2000-2001 (Box 6 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 32)
  - Meeting, 2001 January 25 (Box 6 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 33)
  - Meeting, 2001 March 8 (Box 6 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 34)
  - Meeting, 2001 June 7 (Box 6 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 35)
  - Annual Report and minute of the university Council, 2001 July 1-2002 June 30 (Box 6 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 36)
  - Annual Report, 2001 August 6 (Box 6 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 37)
  - Meeting, 2001 September 6 (Box 6 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 38)
  - Meeting, 2001 October 25 (Box 6 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 39)
  - Meeting, 2001 December 4 (Box 6 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 40)
  - Annual Report, 2001-2002 (Box 6 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 41)
  - Meeting, 2002 February 14 (Box 6 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 42)
  - Meeting, 2002 March 21 (Box 6 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 43)
  - Meeting, 2002 May 9 (Box 6 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 44)
  - Annual Report and minutes of the University Council, 2002 July 10-2003 June 30 (Box 6 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 45)
  - Meeting, 2002 October 3 (Box 6 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 46)
  - Meeting, 2002 November 7 (Box 6 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 47)
  - Meeting, 2002 December 13 (Box 6 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 48)
  - Annual Report, 2002-2003 (Box 6 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 49)
  - Meeting, 2003 April 11 (Box 6 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 50)
  - Meeting, 2003 May 29 (Box 7 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 1)
  - Meeting, 2003 October 9 (Box 7 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 2)
  - Meeting, 2003 November 13 (Box 7 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 3)
  - Meeting, 2003 December 11 (Box 7 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 4)
  - Annual Report, 2003-2004 (Box 7 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 5)
  - Meeting, 2004 February 12 (Box 7 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 6)
  - Meeting, 2004 March 11 (Box 7 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 7)
  - Meeting, 2004 April 22 (Box 7 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 8)
  - Meeting, 2004 June 22 (Box 7 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 9)
  - Agendas and minutes, 2004 July 1-2005 June 30 (Box 7 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 10)
  - Annual Report, 2004-2005 (Box 7 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 11)
  - Annual Report, 2008-2009 (Box 7 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 12)
  - Annual Report, 2009-2010 (Box 7 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 13)
  - Annual Report, 2010-2011 (Box 7 (2-Meeting Records), Folder 14)
  - Meeting Minutes - 3 pm, George Education Center, University at Albany East Campus, School of Public Health Dean's Conference Room, 2010 September 24; 90.63 KB
  - Audio Recording of Meeting, 2010 September 24; 29.45 MB
  - Meeting Minutes - 3 pm, University Hall Room 306, 2010 November 5; 71.96 KB
  - Audio Recording of Meeting, 2010 November 5; 27.78 MB
  - Meeting Minutes - University Hall Room 306, 2011 February 18; 32.93 KB
  - Audio Recording of Meeting, 2011 February 18; 36.75 MB
  - Meeting Minutes - University Hall Room 306, 2011 May 6; 17.5 KB
  - Audio Recording of Meeting, 2011 May 6; 54.35 MB
  - Meeting Minutes - University Hall Room 306, 2011 October 13; 99.6 KB
  - Audio Recording of Meeting, 2011 October 13; 24.28 MB
  - Meeting Minutes - University Hall Room 306, 2011 December 9; 17.9 KB
  - Audio Recording of Meeting, 2011 December 9; 42.25 MB
  - Meeting Minutes - University Hall Room 306, 2012 March 9; 14.34 KB
  - Audio Recording of Meeting, 2012 March 9; 38.33 MB
  - Meeting Minutes - University Hall Room 306, 2012 May 18; 76.41 KB
  - Audio Recording of Meeting, 2012 May 18; 45.92 MB
  - Meeting Minutes - State University System Administration Offices, SUNY Plaza, Albany, NY, 2012 August 15; 103.53 KB
  - Meeting Minutes - University Hall Room 306, 2012 October 5; 139.96 KB
  - Audio Recording of Meeting, 2012 October 5; 108.6 MB
  - Meeting Minutes, 2012 December 7; 74.52 KB
  - Audio Recording of Meeting, 2012 December 7; 69.52 MB
  - Meeting Minutes, 2013 March 28; 77.57 KB
  - Audio Recording of Meeting, 2013 March 28; 45.68 MB
  - Meeting Minutes - University Hall Room 306, 2013 May 10; 11 KB
  - Presentation: "Developing a Strategic Framework for Online Teaching and Learning, 2013 May 10; 555.01 KB
  - Presentation: Student Indebtedness, 2013 May 10; 180.04 KB
  - Supporting Document: SUNY Smart Track Campaign, 2013 May 10; 123.83 KB
  - Presentation: "Rising Student Debt Levels: Institutional Causes and Potential Remedies", 2013 May 10; 885.15 KB
  - Audio Recording of Meeting, 2013 May 10; 47.64 MB
  - Meeting Minutes - University Hall Room 306, 2013 July 17; 11.05 KB
  - Empowering Resolution to Implement the Separation of the College of Nanoscale Science and Engineering and the State University of New York at Albany, 2013 July 17; 26.67 KB
  - Audio Recording from the Meeting, 2013 July 17; 22.17 MB
  - Meeting Minutes - University Hall Room 306, 2013 August 29; 168.66 KB
  - Community Rights & Responsibilities, 2013 August 29; 231.46 KB
  - Community Rights & Responsibilities Appendix C - Standards of Academic Integrity, 2013 August 29; 33.84 KB
  - Community Rights & Responsibilities Appendix L - Double Jurisdiction, 2013 August 29; 10.59 KB
  - Audio Recording from the Meeting, 2013 August 29; 18.67 MB
  - Meeting Minutes - University Hall Room 306, 2013 October 11; 18.37 KB
  - Presentation, 2013 October 11; 1.28 MB
  - Resolution - Non-philanthropic Naming Rights Marketing Agreements, 2013 October 11; 330.39 KB
  - Audio Recording from the Meeting, 2013 October 11; 36.62 MB
  - Meeting Minutes - University Hall Room 306, 2013 December 6; 42.87 KB
  - 2013-14 Budget Presentation, 2013 December 6; 149.5 KB
  - Start-Up NY Plan - Draft, 2013 December 6; 229.38 KB
  - Start-Up NY Attachments, 2013 December 6; 2.45 MB
  - Audio Recording from the Meeting, 2013 December 6; 391.61 MB
  - Meeting Minutes - New York City SUNY Global Center, 116 East 55th Street, 2014 February 27; 44.81 KB
  - Meeting Agenda, 2014 February 27; 13.88 KB
  - Council Resolution Regarding the Recognition Opportunity for the Emeritus Center, 2014 February 27; 234.99 KB
  - 2014 Association of Council Members and College Trustees of the State University of New York Handbook, 2014 February 27; 86.33 KB
  - Audio Recording from the Meeting, 2014 February 27; 91.99 MB
  - Meeting Minutes - University Hall Room 306, 2014 May 9; 30.58 KB
  - Graduate Student Association Report to the Council, 2014 May 9; 180.95 KB
  - University at Albany Alumni Association 2013-2014 Annual Report, 2014 May 9; 1.25 MB
  - Birds-Eye View of Recruitment, Admission, Financial Aid, and Retention of Undergraduate and Graduate Students - PowerPoint Presentation Given by Robert Andrea, Associate Vice Provost, Enrollment Management, Dr. Kevin Williams, Vice Provost and Dean of Graduate Studies, 2014 May 9; 3.19 MB
  - University Council Resolution for Klara Botvinnik, 2014 May 9; 195.42 KB
  - University Council Resolution for Professor Joette Stefl-Mabry, 2014 May 9; 202.44 KB
  - University Council Resolution for Gary Roth, 2014 May 9; 198.11 KB
  - Audio Recording from the Meeting, 2014 May 9; 37.23 MB
  - Meeting Minutes - Mohawk Tower, 22nd Floor, 2014 September 26; 50.74 KB
  - Meeting Agenda, 2014 September 26; 9.6 KB
  - Faculty Governance Council Report, 2014 September 26; 69.74 KB
  - Graduate Student Report, 2014 September 26; 44.91 KB
  - Undergraduate Student Report, 2014 September 26; 116.73 KB
  - Advocacy Center Council Presentation, 2014 September 26; 1.05 MB
  - Resolution Adopting Consent Agenda Meeting Format, 2014 September 26; 7.86 KB
  - Proposed Bylaws Revision - Election of Officers, 2014 September 26; 48.73 KB
  - Recognition of Pierre L. Alrics Service to the University, 2014 September 26; 36.26 KB
  - Recognition of Michael R. Steins Service to the University, 2014 September 26; 35.93 KB
  - Recognition Opportunities for Library Preservation Department and University Athletics, 2014 September 26; 17.43 KB
  - Recognition Opportunity for Athletics Resolution, 2014 September 26; 7.05 KB
  - Athletics Recognition Opportunities, 2014 September 26; 385.56 KB
  - Audio Recording from the Meeting, 2014 September 26; 51.02 MB
  - Meeting Minutes - SUNY Global Center, 116 East 55th St., N.Y., N.Y., 2015 February 27; 72.94 KB
  - Meeting Agenda, 2015 February 27; 9.69 KB
  - The Engineering Profile for the University at Albany, 2015 February 27; 98.82 KB
  - Community Rights Responsibilities 2014-2015 Updates, 2015 February 27; 245.32 KB
  - Summary of Amendment of Community Rights and Responsibilities, 2015 February 27; 46.83 KB
  - SUNY Sexual Assault Response & Prevention Memorandum, 2015 February 27; 196.56 KB
  - SUNY Policies on Sexual Violence Prevention and Response, 2015 February 27; 256.33 KB
  - University Council Resolution - Amendments to Community Rights and, 2015 February 27; 11.19 KB
  - Responsibilities Relative to Sexual Violence Prevention and Response, 2015 February 27; 7.13 KB
  - University Council Resolution - Recognition Opportunity in School of Business Building, 2015 February 27; 6.98 KB
  - University Council Resolution - Recognition Opportunity to Name School of Business Building, 2015 February 27; 109.54 KB
  - Alumni Association Report, 2015 February 27; 147.19 KB
  - Undergraduate Report, 2015 February 27; 26.26 KB
  - Proposed Letter of Intent - Albany Law School, 2015 February 27; 51.05 KB
  - Audio Recording from the Meeting, 2015 February 27; 47.75 MB
  - Meeting Minutes - UNH 306, 2015 May 15; 67.32 KB
  - Meeting Agenda, 2015 May 15; 13.75 KB
  - Attachment A - Minutes from the 2/27/15 Council Meeting, 2015 May 15; 294.02 KB
  - Attachment B - Report on the Governance Council, 2015 May 15; 428.84 KB
  - Attachment C - Graduate Student Association Report, 2015 May 15; 478.15 KB
  - Attachment D - Alumni Report, 2015 May 15; 2.31 MB
  - Attachment E - Council Resolution Affirming contributions to the University Council by Timothy P. Murphy, 2015 May 15; 162.99 KB
  - Audio Recording from the Meeting, 2015 May 15; 40.94 MB
  - Meeting Minutes - UNH 306, 2015 August 7; 45.86 KB
  - Meeting Agenda, 2015 August 7; 20.57 KB
  - Draft Minutes - 5/15/2015, 2015 August 7; 647.11 KB
  - Governance Council Report, 2015 August 7; 582.46 KB
  - Undergraduate Student Report, 2015 August 7; 198.61 KB
  - Graduate Student Report, 2015 August 7; 257.31 KB
  - Resolution Amending Community Rights and Responsibilities, 2015 August 7; 408.48 KB
  - Resolution Affirming the Contributions of Bryant Barksdale, 2015 August 7; 191.11 KB
  - Resolution Affirming the Contributions of Nick Butler, 2015 August 7; 198.61 KB
  - Resolution Affirming the Contributions of Cynthia Fox, 2015 August 7; 196.7 KB
  - Audio Recording from the Meeting, 2015 August 7; 33.65 MB
- Bylaws, 2012 November; 3; 1 Digital Files 1 Digital Files
  - University Council Bylaws, 2012 November; 122.25 KB
- Subject Files, 1964-1997, Undated; 4; 0.66 cubic ft.
  Information on council members and other subjects.
  - Dormitory Names, 1964 October (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 1)